Guide to the Bert Stimmel Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2006 Acquisition, 1785-2005; 20.22; (49 boxes)
  - Computer media
    - Computer disks, undated; (50 computer disks)
      - 3 (REVISED) BACK-UP ENGLAND RETURN UK HER EXCEL BUDDYS PENNY PLA PENNY 1 VARIETY THE BLACK SUNDOWN OXFORD 2 DANCE BUDDYS 5 LONDON FU TO DORSET SOLDRTAL HER EXC 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0033; 1 (Box 47)
      - 1 BEIRUT 1 / BEIRUT 2 BEIRUT 3 / BEIRUT 5 BEIRUT 6 / BEIRUT 7 BEIRUT 8 / BEIRUT 9, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0034; 1 (Box 47)
      - LONDON BIG BEND, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0035; 1 (Box 47)
      - POSTERS 1 PIRATES 4 TURBAN 1 SASHS 1 GOWNS 1 TURBANS 2 GOWN 2 DERVISH 1 DAN-BO 9 TRAVEL 1 REFORM 1 LADYHE 1 TRAVEL 2 TRAVEL 3 PERSIAN 1 HOLYLA 1 LIBAN 1 MAMLUK1 IRAQ 1 EGYPT 1 TURKEY 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0036; 1 (Box 47)
      - NEW FAMILY TREE TEST 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0037; 1 (Box 47)
      - FAMILY TREE MAKER 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0038; 1 (Box 47)
      - HARD DISK COPY1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0039; 1 (Box 47)
      - 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0040; 1 (Box 47)
      - PRACTISE - COSTUME TEXT (DR), 2006-ycal-0116-a-0041; 1 (Box 47)
      - xywrite Bert Stimmel's Caracella disk 1. Bert1.go [Aschii] Bert2.go Bert3.go, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0042; 1 (Box 47)
      - CADDIE MAC LIFE UPON WICKED STAGE NIGHT TRAIN TO ROME EAST --> WEST FASHION, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0043; 1 (Box 47)
      - 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0044 (Box 47)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0045; 1 (Box 47)
      - TRAVELLER1 PICT TRAVELLER2 PICT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0046; 1 (Box 47)
      - MILITARY PICT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0047; 1 (Box 47)
      - A:/ BERT STIMMEL AMISH.Doc MENNON.Doc MENNOS.Doc PENNDU.Doc PENNSY.Doc, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0048; 1 (Box 47)
      - CAIRO 1 CAIRO 2 ("BIZARRE"9, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0049; 1 (Box 47)
      - POSTERS 1 PIRATES 4 TURBAN 1 SASHS 1 GOWNS 1 TURBANS 2 GOWN 2 DERVISH 1 DANBO 9 TRAVEL 1 TRAVEL 2 LADYHE 7 REFORM 1 TRAVEL 3 PERSIAN 1 HOLYLAND 1 LIBAN 1 MAMLUK1 IRAQ 1 EGYPT 1 TURKEY 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0050; 1 (Box 47)
    - Computer disks, undated; (49 computer disks)
      2006-ycal-0116-a-0051 - 2006-ycal-0116-a-0099
      - DISC 1 COPY DESK TOP A, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0051; 1 (Box 48)
      - ENERGY 1 ENERGY 2 17THCENTUR COMMEDI FARRE 1 COMEDIE 2 EXERCISE EXERCI 2 HORIZONS, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0052; 1 (Box 48)
      - TRAVELLER 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0053; 1 (Box 48)
      - ORBIT 1-see3-3-4-6 SIMBEL 1-3-4-5-6-7-see3-9 LIBAN 1-2 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0054; 1 (Box 48)
      - DANCING B DANCE BO DANCE BO2 DANCE BO3 DANCE BO4 DANCE BO5 DANCE BO6 DANCEB07 DANCE BO8 HISTORY 1 HISTORY 2 HISTORY 3 INTRO1 HISTORY 4 THEATRE 0 THEATRE 1 BIBLIOSR MOOR HIST THEMES [illegible] HIST2 HIST3 HIST5 LEAF FABRICS1 FABRIC2 FABRIC3 FABRIC4 FABRIC5 FABRIC6 FABRIC7 SERAGLIO, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0055; 1 (Box 48)
      - A PIRATES2 PIRATES3 ORIENT 1 DRAGOMAN DUTCH1 SERPENT2 HUSSAR 1 MASK 4 GAWAZ 1 OULED1 WO-MEN1 CELESTE1 WOMEN 3 DESERT 3 MEN-WO2 TRALER1 DESERT 4 PIRATES5 PIRATES 3 LADYHES1 TRAVELER EGYPO1 EXHIBIT 2 MAMLUK1 LEGION1 FATNM1 FIGINTRO FIGINTRO 2 FIGINT 3 FILMS1 SASH 1 TURBAN 1 TAPERED TAPEBLUE FIG4 TAPEORAN ATTINE1 MASK4, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0056; 1 (Box 48)
      - DESERT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0057; 1 (Box 48)
      - SULTAN-SEARGLIO, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0058; 1 (Box 48)
      - GAWAZI, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0059; 1 (Box 48)
      - COSTUME - "APPLES", 2006-ycal-0116-a-0060; 1 (Box 48)
      - SIGHT AND SOUND EAST TO WEST FASHION, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0061; 1 (Box 48)
      - A TAPE BLUE SASH 1 TURBAN 1 FIGINTRO 2 FIGINTO 3 FIG 4 TAPERED ORIENT 1 ALHAMBRA TAPEORAN DRAGOMAN DUTCH 1 SERPENT 2 HUSSAR 1 MASK 4 GAWAZI 1 OULED 1 WO-MEN 1 CELESTE 1 WOMEN 3 MEN-WO 1 TRAVEL R1 EGYPO1 DESERET 3 DESERT 4 FILMS 1 LADYHES1 EXHIBIT 2 MAMLLK 1 LEGION 1 FATINIT 1 FIGINTR PIRATES 2 PIRATES 3, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0062; 1 (Box 48)
      - DANCING B DANCE BO DANCE BO 2 DANCE BO 3 DANCE BO4 DANCE BO5 DANCE BO 6 DANCE BO7 DANCE BO 8 HISTORY 1 HISTORY 2 HISTORY 3 HISTORY 4 THEATRE 9 THEATRE 1 BIBLIOSR MOOR HIST THEMES 1 HIST 2 HIST 3 HIST 5 LEAF 1 INTRO 1 PIRATES 4 FABRICS 1 FABRIC 3 FABRC2 FABRIC 4 FABRIC 5 FABRIC 6 FABRIC 7 SERAGLIO, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0063; 1 (Box 48)
      - 3 TITLE 2 ORBIT 1 ORBIT 2 SALLY MIL BITE 3 SIMBLE 9 BITE 4 SIMBLE5, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0064; 1 (Box 48)
      - CRACKER 4 CRAKBBA 1 HATBOX WIKDWO2 ESCAPE WIKDWOR 1 TITLE 2 SALLYMIL FIG LEAF, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0065; 1 (Box 48)
      - TRiPOY1 TRAVELERS, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0066; 1 (Box 48)
      - TRiPOLY1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0067; 1 (Box 48)
      - REWRITES 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0068; 1 (Box 48)
      - SERVANTS CEREMONIES SLAVES, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0069; 1 (Box 48)
      - MYDANCEC DANCE CO 2 DANCE CO 3 ITALY ITALY2 ATUTEL SPAIN 1 CHESTER 2 CHESTER 1 CHESTER 3 PUSS BOOT JUBILEEG DANCE ASC DEVILTIT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0070; 1 (Box 48)
      - TEXT PICT DANCE BOYS, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0071; 1 (Box 48)
      - B HANDS TO HANDS BOYHOOD JIM + CAMILLE SWATTIN AROUND WSSAF WSSAFT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0072; 1 (Box 48)
      - GHASSAN'S PHOTOS AT HIS PARTY FOR MY "80TH BIRTHDAY" TAKEN IN HIS FLAT ON 84TH ST., 2006-ycal-0116-a-0073; 1 (Box 48)
      - 2 OLD VIC 1 OLD VIC 2 OLD VIC 3 LONDON 2 ST.DENIS TAKINAC1 TAKIN2 PARIS 1 OXFORD SS TIGER LONDON 1 SUGARSP1 SUGARSPi RETURN US WATERLOO, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0074; 1 (Box 48)
      - ALAME 1 ALME 2 ALME 3 ALME4 ALME 5 ALME 6 ALME 7 ALME 8 SPAIN 1 SPAIN 2 MOORS 1 MOOR 1 OOR 3 EAST 1 FASHION BLOOMER1 MASK 1 MASK 2 MASK 3 BLUEBEAR SERPENT 1 DESERT 1 EGYPT 1 OPERA 1 BASHA 1 SULTAN 1 MOOR HIST INTRO 1 PIRATES 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0075; 1 (Box 48)
      - TRAVELLER1 TRAVELLER 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0076; 1 (Box 48)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0077; 1 (Box 48)
      - DANCE TEACHING INTRO, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0078; 1 (Box 48)
      - WOMEN AS MEN: DUTCH 1 WO-MEN 1 WOMEN 2 WOMEN 3 LADYHES 1 FATINIZI CELESTE1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0079; 1 (Box 48)
      - DANCING BOYS, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0080; 1 (Box 48)
      - MASKS SPAIN, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0081; 1 (Box 48)
      - GAWAZI BIBLIOGRAPHY GAWAZI 2 EAST TO WEST FASHION LIFE UPON THE W STAGE INTRO NIGHT TRAIN TO ROME, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0082; 1 (Box 48)
      - ALAME 1 ALME 2 ALME 3 ALME 4 ALME 5 ALME 6 ALME 7 ALME 8 SPAIN 1 SPAIN 2 MOORS 1 MOOR 1 OOR3 EAST 1 FASHION 1 BLUEBEAR MASK 1 MASK 2 MASK 3 BLOOMER1 SERPENT 1 DESERT 1 EGYPT 1 OPERA1 BASHA 1 SULTAN 1 MOOR HIST INTRO 1 PIRATES 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0083; 1 (Box 48)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0084; 1 (Box 48)
      - COSTUME FASHIONS (IBM), 2006-ycal-0116-a-0085; 1 (Box 48)
      - REWRITES 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0086; 1 (Box 48)
      - 2 VISIT 1 VISITE 1-2 3-4-5-6 BIZARE 4-2-3 4-5-6-7-8 9-10 INDEX, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0087; 1 (Box 48)
      - 5 SHREW 1 SHREW 2 SHREW 3 SHREW 4 SHREW 5 SHREW 6 SHREW 7 ECHOES 1 ECHOES 2 DREAM 1 DREAM 2 DREAM 3 DREAM 4 INDEX, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0088; 1 (Box 48)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0089; 1 (Box 48)
      - BITE 2 WRONG RED 3 FIG LEAF 4 WIKEDWO1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0090; 1 (Box 48)
      - Tetris Game, Spreadsheet Templates and Data Storage Disk for Brother Work Organizer, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0091; 1 (Box 48)
      - BERT NEW MICROSOFT WORD DOCU DEVIL'S DEVIL'S OUTLET OUTLET2 OUTLET3, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0092; 1 (Box 48)
      - DISC 1 DESKTOP A, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0093; 1 (Box 48)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0094; 1 (Box 48)
      - AFGHANISTAN FACE AND BODY, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0095; 1 (Box 48)
      - A "HANDS TO HANDS" BOYHOOD/JIM + CAMILLE SWATTIN ROUND/ WSSAF WSSAFT/, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0096; 1 (Box 48)
      - B DISC 2 FUJITSU INDVIDUAL SOFTWARE AFGHANISTAN, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0097; 1 (Box 48)
      - B BERT NEW DOCUMENT DEVIL'S DEVILS OUTLET3 OUTLET OUTLET NO. 2 DISC 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0098; 1 (Box 48)
      - A PORTRAITS CARAEQUA MENSAES BACKSTAGE BEIRUT HUT RED LIGHT DISTRICT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0099; 1 (Box 48)
    - Computer disks, undated; (31 computer disks)
      2006-ycal-0116-a-0100 - 2006-ycal-0116-a-0130
      - TRAVELLER 2 PICT DANCE, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0100; 1 (Box 49)
      - TRAVELLER 1 PICT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0101; 1 (Box 49)
      - TURBAN 3, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0102; 1 (Box 49)
      - TURBAN 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0103; 1 (Box 49)
      - TARABUSH 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0104; 1 (Box 49)
      - BERT TEXT-1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0105; 1 (Box 49)
      - ARANUTS 1 MILITARY PICT 1 SAPHIS 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0106; 1 (Box 49)
      - TEXT DANCE 3 MIDDLE-EAST DANCE BEDONINE DANCES (MACWORD 5.1), 2006-ycal-0116-a-0107; 1 (Box 49)
      - "LIFE UPON WICKED STAGE", 2006-ycal-0116-a-0108; 1 (Box 49)
      - DANCE #4, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0109; 1 (Box 49)
      - ARAB DANCES (APPLE MAC), 2006-ycal-0116-a-0110; 1 (Box 49)
      - 1 BEIRUT 1 BERUIT 2 BEIRUT 3 BERUIT 5 BEIRUT 6 BEIRUT 7 BEIRUT 8 BEIRUT 9, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0111; 1 (Box 49)
      - 2 VISIT 1 VISITE 1 VISITE 2 VISITE 3 VISITE 4 VISITE 5 VISITIE 6 BIZARRE 1 BIZARRE 2 BIZARRE 3 BIZARRE 4 BIZARRE 5 BIZARRE 6 BIZARRE 7 BIZARRE 8 BIZARRE 9 BIZARRE 10, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0112; 1 (Box 49)
      - 3 TENTS 1-2-3 4-5-6-7 8-9-10-11, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0113; 1 (Box 49)
      - 4 TRIC 2-3-4 5-6-7-8 9, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0114; 1 (Box 49)
      - 5 SHREW 1 SHREW 2 SHREW 3 SHREW 4 SHREW 5 SHREW 6 SHREW 7 ECHOES 1 ECHOES 2 DREAM 1 DREAM 2 DRREAM 3 DREAM 4 INDEX, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0115; 1 (Box 49)
      - DEVIL'S PLAYGROUND CRACKER 1 CRACKER 2 CRACKER 3 CRACKER 4 WIKDWOR 1 WICKDWO 2 CRACKER 5 (+WIDKWOR1 ON ORANGE DIS) CRACKER BA WIKEDWO 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0116; 1 (Box 49)
      - 2 SS TIGER OLD VIC -1-2-3 LONDON 2 ST.DENIS TAKING AC TAKIN AC 1 SUGAR SP. SUGARSP1 PARIS 1 RETURN US OXFORD WATERLOO LONDON 1, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0117; 1 (Box 49)
      - 3 RETURN WK HER EXCEL BUDDYS PENNY PLA PENNY 1 VARIETY THE BLACK SUNDOWN OXFORD 2 DANCE BUDDYS 5 LONDON FU TO DORSET SOLDRTAL HER EXCEL 2, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0118; 1 (Box 49)
      - 4 MY DANCE C DANCE CO 2 DANCE CO 3 ITALY 1 ITALY 2 ATVTEL SPAIN 1 CHESTER 1 CHESTER 2 CHESTER 3 PUSS BOOT JUBILEEG DANCE ASC DEVILTIT, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0119; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0120; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0121; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0122; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0123; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0124; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0125; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0126; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0127; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0128; 1 (Box 49)
      - [no label information], 2006-ycal-0116-a-0129; 1 (Box 49)
      - ENERGY1 ENERGY2 17CENTUR COMMEDI FARCE1 COMEDIE2 EXERCISE EXERCI2 HORIZONS, 2006-ycal-0116-a-0130; 1 (Box 49)
- May 2006 Acquisition, 1944-1982; 0.21; (1 box)
  Former call number: Uncat Za File 706.
  - Color photograph of Bert Stimmel in Texas, 1982 (Box 50)
  - Certificate of membership for Bert Stimmel from the Distinguished Flying Cross Society, with related papers, including notice of discharge (photocopies), 1944-1945 (Box 50)